摩妮卡 这真是史上最棒的 感恩节大餐 太好吃了
Monica, that was the best Thanksgiving dinner ever.
你把我们撑死了
It was so good. I think you killed us.
我连一口都吃不下了
I couldn't possibly eat another bite.
我要吃甜的
I need something sweet.
有人想看电视吗？
Does anyone wanna watch TV?
好啊
Yeah. Sure.
摩妮卡 你的遥控器按不动
Monica, your remote doesn't work.
你得把它拿起来对准
Phoebe, you have to lift it and point.
噢
Oh.
算了
Oh, forget it.
你们知道吗？
Hey, you know what we should all do?
我们应该来玩感恩告白游戏
We should play that game where everyone says one thing they're thankful for.
我要说 感谢今年的秋天这么美
Oh, I... I am thankful for this beautiful fall we've been having.
- 说得真好   - 好的 乔伊
- Very nice.      - Sweet, Joe.
那天我在等公车
Yeah, the other day, I was at the bus stop...
突然吹来一阵秋风
...and this lovely fall breeze came in out of nowhere...
把一个女生的裙子吹了起来
...and blew this chick's skirt right up.
对了 我还要感谢丁字裤
Oh, which reminds me, I'm also thankful for thongs.
与其说它是内裤 不如说是一种伟大工程
It's not so much an underpant as it is a feat of engineering.
料子那么少 效果却那么大
It's amazing how much they can do with so little material.
它还会戏弄你 有穿吗？没穿吗？
And the way they play with your mind. I mean, is it there? Is it not there?
你知道你还在碎碎念吗？
Are you aware that you're still talking?
有没有人要感谢丁字裤以外的东西？
Is anyone thankful for anything else besides a thong?
呵呵 我不知道该怎么挑
Huh. I don't know what to pick.
我更感谢为我的离婚 还是我驱逐？
Am I more thankful for my divorce, or my eviction? Hmm.
哇哦 我还以为你会没得谢
Wow, see, and I didn't think you'd be able to come up with anything.
抱歉 这是最惨的一次感恩节
I'm sorry. It's just this is the worst Thanksgiving ever.
不行 我才是悲惨感恩节盟主
No, no, no. I am the king of bad Thanksgivings.
你不能挟失败的婚姻空降…
You can't just swoop in here with your bad marriage...
抢了我的宝座
...and take that away from me.
你又要说…
You're not gonna tell the whole story...
你爸妈离婚的事了？
...about how your parents got divorced, are you?
别这样嘛
No, no.
快点 我想听
Come on. I want to hear it.
没有钱德扫兴就不算感恩节了
It wouldn't be Thanksgiving without Chandler bumming us out.
这跟游行一样是一项传统
It's a tradition, like the parade.
如果游行也出轨离家 抛妻弃子的话
If the parade decided it was gay, moved out and abandoned its entire family.
钱德
Now, Chandler, dear.
爸爸和我要离婚
Just because your father and I are getting a divorce...
并不代表我们不爱你
...doesn't mean we don't love you.
这只是…
It just means...
代表他上床的对像是男仆 不是我
...he would rather sleep with the houseboy than with me.
小少爷还要火鸡吗？
More turkey, Mr. Chandler?
你说得对 你的更惨 你是悲惨感恩节盟主
You're right, yours is worse. You are the king of bad Thanksgivings.
不一定 我有一次更惨
I don't know about that. I've got one that's worse.
真的吗？惨过…
Really? Worse than
"小少爷还要火鸡"吗？
"More turkey, Mr. Chandler?"
小少爷跟仆人有仇吗？
Did the little rich boy had a problem with the butler?
对 我的更惨
Yes, mine's worse.
(1862年感恩节)
[GUNFIRE AND BOMBS EXPLODING]
还要绷带 还要绷带
More bandages! More bandages!
快 能在给我一些绷带吗？
Please, can I get some more bandages in here?
这个人快死… 啊
This man is... Aah!
不会吧
Oh, no.
今生的才算
In this life, Phoebe.
今生是吧
Oh, this life.
哦 是的 不 那钱德的比较惨
Oh, okay. No, Chandler's is worse.
记得前世的事一定很酷
Man, it must be so cool remembering stuff like that.
我都没有前世的记忆
I don't have any past life memories.
当然没有 你是新生命
Of course, you don't, sweetie. You're brand-new.
我知道摩妮卡最惨的感恩节
I know Monica's worst Thanksgiving.
- 那个就别提了   - 说嘛
- Oh, let's not tell this story.      - Oh, come on.
哦 不 我知道 我知道
Oh, no! I know! I know!
就是摩妮卡的火鸡 卡在乔伊头上那次
It's the one where Joey got Monica's turkey stuck on his head.
- 什么？ - 什么？
- What?     - What?
乔伊头上卡了只火鸡？
Joey got a turkey stuck on his head?
其实不是那样
Hey, it's not like it sounds.
其实就是那样
It's exactly like it sounds.
你好？
Hello?
- 菲比？ - 乔伊？
- Phoebe?     - Joey?
怎么了？
What's going on?
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
我知道
I know.
它卡住了
It's stuck.
小心台阶 它怎么会跑到你头上？
Step. How did it get on?
是我套上去想吓钱德
I put it on to scare Chandler.
天哪 摩妮卡一定会气死
Oh, my God. Monica's going to totally freak out.
那就赶快帮我拿下来
Well, then help me get it off.
而且这里面好臭
Plus, it smells really bad in here.
当然很臭 你的头塞在动物尸体的屁股里
Of course it smells really bad. You have your head up a dead animal.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
你替火鸡涂… 我的天哪
Hey, did you get the turkey...? Oh, my God!
噢 我的天
Oh, my God!
那是谁？
Who is that?
乔伊啦
It's Joey.
你在干什么？你是在搞笑吗？
What are you doing? Is this supposed to be funny?
不是搞笑 是吓人
No, it's not supposed to be funny. It's supposed to be scary.
马上给我拿掉
Get that off now.
拿不掉 卡住了
I can't. It's stuck.
我不管 我爸妈的20个客人
Well, I don't care. That turkey has to feed 20 people.
可不能就着你的头吃
They're not going to eat it off your head.
先别急 大家一起想办法
Hold on, okay? Let's just all think.
好吧 我知道了 菲比？
Okay, I got it. Phoebe?
好吧 你扛
All right. You pull.
我尽量把腿撑开
I'm gonna spread the legs as wide as I can.
- 乔伊 现在不要闹   - 对不起 好吧 对不起
- Joey, now is not the time.     - Yeah. Sorry. Right, sorry.
好 数到一 二
Okay, count to three. One, two...
三
...three.
成功了 我吓到你了
It worked. I scared you. I knew it. Ha, ha!
- 大哥 我在这里   - 是 你在那儿 哈 哈
- I'm over here, big guy.      - Yeah, you are. Ha, ha!
我吓到你了
I scared you. Whoo!
你看起来真的很白痴
You did look like an idiot.
白痴的不只是我
Hey, I wasn't the only one who looked like an idiot, all right?
罗斯有一次想说"冬南瓜"
Remember when Ross tried to say "butternut squash"...
结果讲成"南冬瓜"
...and it came out, "squatternut bosh"?
的确一样白痴
Yeah, that's the same.
那就是我最惨的感恩节
That's it. That's my worst Thanksgiving.
等等 瑞秋说的不可能是那次
Oh, wait. That can't be the one that Rachel was talking about...
因为她根本不知道那件事
...because she didn't even know that that happened.
- 所以是哪次？ - 哪次？
- So, what's yours?     - What was it?
我真的不想提这件事
Um, I really don't wanna tell this story.
噢 讲嘛 摩妮卡
Oh, come on, Monica.
重温悲惨的回忆 是感恩节的精神
Reliving past pain and getting depressed is what Thanksgiving's all about.
至少我觉得是 还有原住民的帮忙
You know, for me, anyway. And, of course, the Indians.
最不希望我提的绝对是你
Look, of all people, you do not want me to tell this story.
什么意思？
What is that supposed to mean?
摩妮卡 应该是瑞秋来了
Monica, I think Rachel's here.
我来开
I'll get it.
- 感恩节快乐   - 我不快乐
- Happy Thanksgiving.     - Not for me.
奇普和我分手了
Chip and I broke up.
为什么？
Oh. Why?
怎么了？
Well, what happened?
我爸妈不是要出门 奇普不是要来…
You know how my parents are out of town, and Chip was gonna come over?
对 对 你要给他
Yeah, yeah. And you were gonna give him, you know...
你的花芯
...your "flower."
摩妮卡 你能不能直接说做爱？
Okay, Monica, can you just call it sex?
你那样讲让我浑身发毛
It really creeps me out when you call it that.
还有 在做的时候
Okay, and by the way...
男人的那里不叫他的温柔
...while we're at it, a guy's thing is not called his "tenderness."
相信我
Believe me.
- 嗨   - 瑞秋
- Hi.     - Hi, Rachel.
- 感恩节快乐   - 你也是
- Happy Thanksgiving.     - You too, sweetheart.
嘿
Hey.
噢 嗨
Oh. Hi.
各位
Uh, everyone...
这是钱德
...this is Chandler.
我的室友兼我们乐团的主唱 呵
My roommate and lead singer of our band. Heh.
罗斯
Ross?
噢 这是摩妮卡
Oh. This is Monica.
嗨 我是罗斯的妹妹
Hi, I'm Ross' little sister.
好
Okay.
欢迎你来 钱德
I'm so glad you could come, Chandler.
我们这儿有很多吃的 希望你饿了
We've got plenty of food, so I hope you're hungry.
噢 妈 不不 钱德痛恨感恩节
Oh, Mom, no, no, Chandler hates Thanksgiving...
他不吃感恩节食物
...and doesn't eat any Thanksgiving food.
那还真是欢迎啊
Oh. Well, I'm so glad you brought him here, then.
嘿 钱德 额…
Hey, Chandler, um...
我可以帮你煮起司通心面
If you want, I can make you some macaroni and cheese for dinner.
只要当年的清教徒没吃我就吃
As long as the Pilgrims didn't eat it, then I'm in.
讨厌
Damn it.
额 瑞秋…
So, uh, Rach...
我去上大学不在？
Does it...? Does it feel weird around here now?
你会不会觉得怪怪的？
You know, since I've been away at college?
噢
Oh.
那倒不会
No, not really.
那就好
That's cool.
那你
So...
奇普居然为了那个花痴南西 而甩了我
Ugh! I cannot believe Chip dumped me for that slut, Nancy Branson.
我再也不跟他约会了
I am never going out with him again.
他再怎么求我也没用
I don't care how much he begs.
他有了南西 应该不会求你了
I think his begging days are over, now that he's with Nancy Branson.
你知道吗？我受够高中男生了
You know what? I've just had it with high-school boys.
他们全是些愚蠢的
They're just silly.
又笨又呆的小毛头
They're just silly, stupid boys.
我要开始跟男人交柱
I'm gonna start dating men.
茱蒂 对不起
Uh, I'm sorry, Judy.
我找不到你和杰克要的碗公
I couldn't find that bowl you and Jack were looking for.
叫爸爸妈妈吧 俗辣
Call them Mom and Dad, you loser.
摩妮卡
Monica.
钱德
Hey, Chandler?
起司通心面好吃吗？
Did you like the macaroni and cheese?
很好吃 你应该去当厨师
Oh, yeah. It was great. You should be a chef.
好啊
Okay.
你猜怎样？
Guess what.
南西很花痴的传闻都是假的
All this stuff about Nancy Branson being a slut was all a rumor.
所以奇普甩了她 他今天晚上想来找我
Chip dumped her, and he wants to come over to my house tonight.
- 太棒了   - 就是啊
- Oh, that is so great.     - I know.
天哪 要是你和奇普晚上做了
Oh, gosh. Listen, if you and Chip do it tonight...
你一定会把细节都告诉我的？
...um, promise me you'll tell me everything?
那当然 其实也没什么 我们应该有做过一次
Oh, totally, totally. It's not that big a deal. We already kind of did it once, you know.
我知道 但这回你定能确定
I know, but this time you're gonna definitely know whether or not you did it.
我知道
I know.
奇普还保证 这次会持续一整首歌的长度
Oh, and Chip promised that this time it would last at least for an entire song.
我晚上打算约瑞秋出去
So I'm thinking of asking Rachel out tonight.
你知道 弹我们上周写的那首歌给她听
You know, maybe playing her that song we wrote last week.
- 《忧愁的背包》对吗   - 对的
- "Emotional Knapsack"? Right on.     - Right on.
不过不要拖太久 好吗？我们还要去试用假身份证
Oh, uh, but don't take long, okay? Because we're testing our fake ID's tonight.
对吧 克里夫艾维瑞兹？
Right, Clifford Alvarez?
听着 罗兰陈
Listen, Roland Cheng...
如果一切顺利 我们搞不好不会回来
...if things go well, I may be out with her all night.
兄弟 别丢下我
Dude, don't do that to me.
没关系 你可以留下来 我爸妈不会介意
Oh, no. It's cool, you can stay here. My parents won't mind.
不是 我不想整晚 跟你的肥猪妹妹在一起
It's not that. I don't wanna be stuck here all night with your fat sister.
嘿
Hey.
摩妮卡 为什么不把这些派吃完？
Monica, why don't you finish off these pies?
冰箱塞不下了
I don't have any more room in the fridge.
不了
No.
不 谢谢
No, thank you.
好吧 茱蒂 你感功了
Well, Judy, you did it.
她终于吃不下了
She's finally full.
我说你肥？
I called you fat?
- 我完全不记得   - 我可记得
- I don't even remember that.     - Well, I do.
对不起 真的 我那时候很愚蠢
I'm so sorry. I really am. But, come on, I was an idiot back then.
我还在"轰"的演唱会上 冲上台大叫
I rushed the stage at a Wham! Concert, for crying out loud.
你居然说她肥
Oh, I can't believe you called her fat.
你居然让乔治麦可赏你耳光
I can't believe you let George Michael slap you.
真的很抱歉
I am really sorry.
我太差劲了 真是对不起
That is so terrible. I'm so, so sorry.
其实我说的不是那次感恩节
Actually, that's not the Thanksgiving I was talking about.
- 是 就是   - 不是 我说的是…
- Yes, it was.     - No, it wasn't. It was actually...
威恩节结束 准备过圣诞节吧
Thanksgiving's over. Get ready for Christmas.
谁要去买圣诞树？
Who wants to get a Christmas tree?
我有最可爱的圣诞节故事
Oh, no. I have the cutest Christmas story.
我们想听摩妮卡的感恩节故事
We wanna hear Monica's Thanksgiving story.
我的故事里有小矮人断成两截
Fine, all right. Mine had a dwarf that got broke in half.
不过 你知道的 随便
But, you know, whatever.
(1988年感恩节)瑞秋 你妈说你又转系了
So, Rachel, your mom tells me you changed your major again?
没办法
Oh, yeah, I had to.
心理系馆旁边很难停车
There was never any parking by the Psychology building.
- 嗨 瑞秋   - 哦 嗨
- Hi, Rachel.     - Oh, hi.
- 你的新鼻子真漂亮   - 杰克
- Wow. Love your new nose.      - Jack.
怎样？威尔森医生是个艺术家
What? Dr. Wolfson's an artist.
他帮我点掉一堆痣
He removed my mole cluster.
你要看吗？
Want to see?
我去开 不 让我去
No, God. Please, let me.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 感恩节快乐     - 嗨
- Happy Thanksgiving.   - Hi.
你的发型变了好多
God, your hair sure is different.
耶 我们刚才还在讲
Yeah, we were just talking about that.
我们以前真的好蠢
Can't we can't believe how stupid we used to look.
摩妮卡呢？
So, uh, where's Monica?
她在楼上 摩妮卡
She's upstairs. Monica.
快下来 人都到齐了
Come down, everyone's here.
罗斯 瑞秋和那个感恩节的男生
Ross, Rachel and the boy who hates Thanksgiving.
钱德
Hi, Chandler.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
我的衣服有脏东西吗？
Is there something on my dress?
你变了好多 好漂亮
You just... You look so different. Terrific.
那件裙子 那个身材
That dress, that body...
- 喂   - 抱歉
- Dude.     - Sorry.
对 摩妮卡瘦了 太好了
Yes, yes, Monica is thin. It's wonderful.
但我们比较关心罗斯的新女友
But what we really want to hear about is Ross' new girlfriend.
噢 妈… 好吧
Oh, Mom... Okay.
好吧 她叫卡萝
Um, ahem, her name is Carol...
她很漂亮 很聪明
...and she's really pretty and smart.
她是长曲棍球和高尔夫球校队
And, uh, she's on the lacrosse team and the golf team.
很厉害吧？
Can you believe it?
她两个校队都打
She plays for both teams.
钱德 那就晚餐见罗
So, Chandler, I guess I'll see you at dinner.
- 喂   - 抱歉
- Dude.     - Sorry.
天哪
Oh, my God.
真是酷毙了
That was so awesome.
你完全报了一箭之仇
You totally got him back for calling you fat.
他的口水流了满地
He was just drooling all over you.
- 感觉一定很过瘾   - 一点也不过瘾
- That must have felt so great.     - Well, it didn't.
什么？
What?
没错 我很漂亮
Yeah, I mean, I look great.
感觉很轻盈 心脏的毛病也没了
And yeah, I feel great, and, yeah, my heart's not in trouble anymore.
等等 等等
Blah, blah, blah.
但我还是觉得没报到仇
I just don't feel like I got him back, you know?
我想狠狠的羞辱他
I mean, I just want to humiliate him.
我想让他光着身体
I want him to be, like, naked...
再指着他大笑
...and I want to point at him and I wanna laugh.
好 搞不好可以
Okay. That, we may be able to do.
怎么做？
How?
男人要做爱之前都会脱光衣服
Well, guys tend to get naked before they're gonna have sex.
什么？我这么努力瘦这么多
What? I mean, I didn't work this hard and lose all this weight...
可不是为了把花芯给他那种人
...just so I could give my flower to someone like him.
好 第一 你再那样讲 保证没有人会要
Okay, first of all, if you keep calling it that, no one is ever gonna take it.
第二 又不是要你来真的
And then second of all, you're not gonna actually have sex with him.
只是要你误导他
You're just gonna make him think that you are.
- 也对   - 耶
- Yeah.   - Yeah.
等他脱光了
And then when he's naked...
我就把他赶出去锁上门
...I can throw him out, lock the door...
让所有的邻居耻笑他
...and all our neighbors will just humiliate him.
那你就绝对报了仇
And then you will definitely get him back.
我要怎么误导他？
Okay, so how do I make him think I want to have sex?
额 我知道了
Uh, Oh! Here's what you do.
假装什么都能让你兴奋
Just act like everything around you turns you on.
- 什么意思？ - 就是什么都能挑动你
- What do you mean?     - Well, like, anything can be sexy.
像…像这条擦碗巾
Like, um... Oh, okay. Like this dish towel.
哦 哦
Ooh, ooh.
它的触感好舒服
This feels so good against my cheek.
如果我热了就可以拿它来吸汗
And if I get a little hot, I can just dab myself with it.
或是把它放在腿边 一边跟他说话…
Or I can bring it down to my side and maybe run it through my fingers...
一边玩弄
...while I talk to him.
- 这个我会   - 好 很好
- I can do that.     - Okay, good, good, good.
忙着呢 他来了 他来了
Get busy. He's coming. He's coming.
- 嘿 怎么了？ - 你好
- Hey, what's up?     - Hey.
摩妮卡 你能不能帮我煮
I was wondering if you could make me some mac and cheese...
去年那种通心面
...like last year?
没问题
I'd love to.
哦
Ooh.
我好喜欢起司通心面
I love macaroni and cheese.
我好喜欢这个盒子的触感
I love the way this box feels against my cheek.
- 好   - 喔 我好喜欢红萝卜
- Okay.     - Ooh, and I love carrots.
哦
Oh!
有时我喜欢把它们这样夹着
Sometimes I like to put them between my fingers.
像这样
Like this.
然后放在腿边跟你说话
And hold them down here while I talk to you.
觉得很热的时候 我喜欢…
Um, and, you know, if I get really hot...
拿起这把刀
...um, I like to pick up this knife.
把冰凉的刀身靠在…
And, um, I put the cool steel...
身上
...against, um...
亲爱的
...my body.
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
我很好
I'm fine.
- 什么状况？ - 20岁男性
- What do got?     - Twenty-year-old male.
右脚拇趾被切到
He's got a severed toe on his right foot.
喔
Ow!
别撞到他的脚好吗？
Could you please not do that feet first?
你明知他是拇趾被切到 你刚才也说了
You know where his injury is. Severed toe, you just said it!
这里写说刀子刺穿鞋子
It says here the knife went right through your shoe.
那当然 他穿的是草鞋
Of course it did. They're made of wicker.
- 断指带来了吗？ - 哦 是的
- Did you bring the toe?     - Oh, yes.
有在这里冰着
I have it right here on ice.
放心 我们会把它缝…
Don't worry, son. We'll just reattach it and then...
- 怎么了？ - 你带了一块红萝卜来
- What is it?     - You brought a carrot.
- 什么？ - 这不是你的脚趾
- What?     - This isn't your toe.
这是一小块很冰的红萝卜
This is a small, very cold piece of carrot.
你带红萝卜来？
You brought a carrot?
天哪
Oh, my God.
我的厨房里有一截断趾
There's a toe in my kitchen.
对不起 我马上回去拿
God, I'm sorry. I'll go back and get it.
来不及了 我们只能直接缝合
It's too late. All we can do is sew up the wound.
- 我需要我的脚趾头   - 好吧
- Without my toe? I need my toe.     - Okay.
等一下 我很快 爸 让我开你的保时捷
No, no, no. I can go really fast. Dad, give me the keys to your Porsche.
我才不会上当
Oh, I'm not falling for that one.
这就是我断趾的原因？因为我说你肥？
That's why I lost my toe? Because I called you fat?
我不是故意的 那是意外
I didn't mean to cut it off. It was an accident.
我就因为这样被叫了一整年的 跛脚趾头先生？
That's why for an entire year people called me Sir Limps-a-lot?
对不起嘛
I'm sorry.
又不是一整根脚趾头
It wasn't your whole toe.
好吧 我少了趾尖
Yeah, well, I miss the tip.
趾尖最棒
It's the best part.
趾尖有指甲
It has the nail.
钱德…
Chandler...
跛脚趾头先生
Sir Limps-a-lot.
那是我想出来的
I came up with that.
你好无聊
You're a dork.
- 我真不敢相信   - 钱德 我都道歉了
- I can't believe this.     - Chandler, I said I was sorry.
道歉也换不回 我那思乡情切的小趾尖
Yeah, well, "sorry" doesn't bring back the little piggy that cried all the way home.
我就知道今天会发生这种事 我恨感恩节和这一天的一切
I hate this stupid day and everything about it.
- 回见   - 等等 钱德
- I'll see you later.     - Wait, Chandler.
过来
Come here.
有什么我能做的吗？
Is there anything I can do? Anything?
有 让我静一静
Yeah, just leave me alone for a little while.
噢 我是一只鸭子 呱呱呱 一天到晚都快乐
Oh, I'm a duck. I go quack-quack. I'm happy all the time.
别试了
Nice try.
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait.
- 摩妮卡   - 你看
- Look, Monica...     - Look.
没有用的
This is not gonna work.
接下来绝对有用
I bet this will work.
你真绝 我爱你
You're so great. I love you.
什么？
What?
没事 我说"你真绝" 然后就没说话了
Nothing. I said you're so great, and then I just stopped talking.
你说你爱我 我真不敢相信
You said you loved me. I can't believe this.
我没有
No, I didn't.
- 你有   - 我没有
- Yes, you did.     - No, I didn't.
你爱我
You love me.
不 别再说了
No, I don't. Stop it, stop it, stop it.
(1915年感恩节)
纱布
Gauze!
纱布 这里需要纱布
Gauze! I need to get some gauze in here!
请再给我一些纱…
Can I please get some more gauze?
真是越来越扯了
This is getting ridiculous.